A Guide to the Correspondence of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, 1972-1976
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Correspondence of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors 1972-1976
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/2.772
This collection consists of 400 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No access without written permission of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors.
Acquisition Information
This collection is an archival transfer of the Board of Visitors, Pavillion VIII East Lawn University of Virginia on 1977 August 3.
Scope and Content Information
Correspondence concerning personnel actions including letters of appointment, re-appointment, promotions, title changes, special salary actions, and resignations for the University and Clinch Valley College.
Organization/Arrangement
Box 1: Personnel actions, Clinch Valley College, elections, re-elections, promotions, leave of absences, resignations, appointments 1972-1974, Personnel actions, appointments and re-appointments 1975 October 3- 1976 May 28, Personnel actions changes of title 1975 Oct 3-1976 May 28, Personnel actions, elections 1975 Oct 3, Personnel actions elections 1976 Jan 23, Personnel actions elections 1976 Mar 26, Personnel actions elections 1976 May 28, Personnel actions leaves of absences 1976 May 28.
Box 2: Personnel actions, promotions 1975-1976, Personnel actions re-elections 1975-Oct 3, 1976 Jan 23, Personnel actions, re-elections change of re-election re-appointments 1976 Mar 26, May 28, Personnel actions resignations 1975-1976, Personnel actions special salary actions 1975 Oct 3.
Contents List
- Personnel actions, Clinch Valley College, elections, re-elections, promotions, leave of absences, resignations, appointments 1972-1974 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, appointments and reappointments 1975 Oct 3 - 1976 May 28 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, changes of title 1975 Oct 3 - 1976 May 28 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, elections 1975 Oct 3 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, elections 1976 Jan 23 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, elections 1976 Mar 26 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, elections 1976 May 28 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, leaves of absences 1976 (Box 1)
- Personnel actions, promotions 1975-1976 (Box 2)
- Personnel actions, re-elections 1975 Oct 3, 1976 Jan 23 (Box 2)
- Personnel actions, re-elections, change of re-election, re-appointments 1976 Mar 26, May 28 (Box 2)
- Personnel actions, resignations 1975-1976 (Box 2)
- Personnel actions, special salary actions 1975 Oct 3 (Box 2)